<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Devil\'s Advocates</string>
    <string name="start_game_button">Start Game</string>
    <string name="instructions_button">How To Play</string>
    <string name="settings_button">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_instructions">How To Play</string>
    <string name="instructions_page">
        "Welcome to Devil's Advocates, a pass-and-play drinking game. After starting a game, the "
        "application will prompt you to enter all player names. After this is complete, the game "
        "will start.\n\n"

        "The game consists of rounds. Each round, two players will be selected to explain something "
        "(usually something terrible) regardless of if they disagree with it or don't understand it.
        "A judge is also selected who holds the phone, reads the topics, and selects the winner. "
        "The players must then rant in favor of their topic for the specified time without stopping
        "or repeating themselves. After both players have finished, the judge must decide who wins the round "
        "based on the strength of the argument and how well the person flowed (i.e. how well he/she "
        "spoke without pausing or repeating).\n\n"

        "Then, the winner of the round will cycle out and the loser will stay for the next round. "
        "The judge must sentence the loser by drinking. The loser has to drink an equal amount. "
        "The game ends when everyone gets either too drunk or too bored to keep playing.\n\n"

        "This game is recommended for 5+ players. As in, more than five players. But yes, also for "
        "people over the age of five.\n\n"

        "The instructions above assume the default settings.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">Gameplay</string>

    <string-array name="round_times_options">
        <item>10 seconds</item>
        <item>20 seconds</item>
        <item>30 seconds</item>
        <item>40 seconds</item>
        <item>50 seconds</item>
        <item>60 seconds</item>
        <item>69 seconds</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="round_times_values">
        <item>10</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>69</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">App Preferences</string>

    <string name="title_activity_initial_game_screen">Game Start: Add Players</string>
    <string name="player_name_input">Player Name</string>
    <string name="player_name_input_too_long">Invalid name.</string>
    <string name="player_name_too_many">Too many players.</string>

    <string-array name="game_topics">
        <item>The pros and cons of trimming your pubes with fire</item>
        <item>Why you should drink your own piss</item>
        <item>How you feel about pineapple on pizza</item>
        <item>The real identy of Tommy Wiseau</item>
        <item>How Ted Cruz is the Zodiac Killer</item>
        <item>Why curling is the most erotic Olympic sport</item>
        <item>What happens to socks that disappear</item>
        <item>The health benefits of anal chugging whiskey</item>
        <item>The plot of the Bible</item>
        <item>Why you should vacation in North Korea</item>
        <item>The pros and cons of eating ass</item>
        <item>The pros and cons of using mashed potatoes as lube</item>
        <item>How fuckin\' magnets work</item>
        <item>Why you should start using heroin</item>
        <item>Why single-ply toilet paper is the best</item>
        <item>The health benefits of huffing gas</item>
        <item>Why Kanye West should run for president</item>
        <item>Why smoking meth is a great weight loss program</item>
        <item>Why male models?</item>
        <item>Why Nick Cage is the sexiest film star</item>
        <item>Why Die Hard is the best Christmas movie</item>
        <item>Why the next Wolverine movie should star Danny DeVito</item>
        <item>Bird Law</item>
        <item>The life lessons learned from Jackass</item>
        <item>How to dispose of a dead body</item>
        <item>Everything you know about the platypus</item>
        <item>The IUPAC rules for naming organic compounds</item>
        <item>The causes of the Israeli-Palestine conflict </item>
        <item>How Santa used to be real until JFK had him killed</item>
        <item>How dwarfs were invented by Germany</item>
        <item>How the fluoride is turning the friggin\' frogs gay</item>
        <item>How to break your back most effectively</item>
        <item>Why driving tests should be administered in GTA V</item>
        <item>Why the Wii remote is the best sex toy</item>
        <item>Why you play video games with a laptop trackpad</item>
        <item>Why wiping your ass is overrated</item>
        <item>The benefits of self-circumcision</item>
        <item>The pros and cons of getting a penis tattooed on your face</item>
        <item>How to kill someone with a pool noodle</item>
        <item>Why steak sauce is great for your hair</item>
        <item>Why Pastafarianism is the one true religion</item>
        <item>How to frame someone for murder</item>
        <item>How to rap</item>
        <item>Why you should wear clothes made of meat</item>
        <item>The truth that Stevie Wonder isn\'t really blind</item>
        <item>Why straight sex is gay</item>
        <item>Why pulling out is the best contraceptive</item>
        <item>The uses of spaghetti in the bedroom</item>
        <item>Why you should learn to speak Malayalam</item>
        <item>Life</item>
        <item>Why it\'s called a pair of pants when it\'s just one thing</item>
        <item>If free will exists or not</item>
        <item>Cryptocurrencies</item>
        <item>How They Don\'t Think It Be Like It Is but It Do</item>
        <item>The best techniques for concealing boners</item>
        <item>How to smuggle drugs in your anus</item>
        <item>Why you should microwave milk</item>
        <item>Your dream to be a pro Russian Roulette player</item>
        <item>The lyrical significance of Lil’ Pump’s “Gucci Gang”</item>
        <item>How to punch spiders</item>
        <item>How to play the French Horn</item>
        <item>The difference between left and right without using an example</item>
        <item>The duck rape arms race</item>
        <item>What is an integral in mathematics</item>
        <item>How to suck dick well</item>
        <item>How Spongebob is anti-semitic</item>
        <item>Why you need to get breast implants</item>
        <item>Why you should eat raw meat</item>
        <item>The correct form for doing cock pushups</item>
        <item>Why mayonnaise makes great shaving cream</item>
        <item>Why air conditioning is for pussies</item>
        <item>The best way to find a cheap hooker</item>
        <item>Why you prefer small dicks</item>
        <item>How squids reproduce</item>
        <item>Why you should drop acid in church</item>
        <item>The plot of War and Peace</item>
        <item>How to change a lightbulb without using any nouns</item>
        <item>How to speedrun getting diabetes</item>
        <item>That pyramids were built by ancient aliens as UFO hangars</item>
        <item>How New Zealand doesn\'t actually exist</item>
        <item>How the lottery was only invented to catch time travellers</item>
        <item>That the Earth is flat</item>
        <item>Why you should use ghost pepper juice as contact solution</item>
        <item>Why you should buy a boat</item>
        <item>The rules of Cricket</item>
        <item>What is defined as a catch under NFL rules</item>
        <item>How the danger of asbestos is a corporate hoax</item>
        <item>How the mentally handicapped are all actually spies</item>
        <item>That lakes were invented to hide lizard people bases</item>
        <item>Why the U.S. should invade Canada</item>
        <item>The sexuality of snow</item>
        <item>What is a Ponzi scheme and how to start one</item>
        <item>The entire plot of Lord of the Rings</item>
        <item>The entire plot of The Godfather I and II</item>
        <item>Why inner city Baltimore is a great place to start a family</item>
        <item>Conciousness</item>
        <item>Why you should mix eraser shavings with your trail mix</item>
        <item>The pros and cons of exposing your genitals to radiation</item>
        <item>The superior leadership skills of Kim Jong-Un</item>
        <item>Why you should wear socks with sandals</item>
        <item>How to not get caught cheating</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
