<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Devil\'s Advocates</string>
    <string name="start_game_button">Start Game</string>
    <string name="instructions_button">How To Play</string>
    <string name="settings_button">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_instructions">How To Play</string>
    <string name="instructions_page">
        "Welcome to Devil's Advocates, a pass-and-play drinking game. After starting a game, the "
        "application will prompt you to enter all player names. After this is complete, the game "
        "will start.\n\n"

        "The game consists of rounds. Each round, two players will be selected to argue in favor of "
        "something (usually something terrible). A judge is also selected. The players must then "
        "rant in favor of their topic for the specified time without stopping or repeating "
        "themselves. After both players have finished, the judge must decide who wins the round "
        "based on the strength of the argument and how well the person flowed (i.e. how well he/she "
        "spoke without pausing or repeating).\n\n"

        "Then, the winner of the round will cycle out and the loser will stay for the next round. "
        "The judge must sentence the loser by drinking. The loser has to drink an equal amount."
        "When a player refuses to argue in favor of something, drink, or otherwise chooses to quit, "
        "they are eliminated from the game. The game ends when there are only two people remaining. "
        "These two people are the winners. I didn't think of a way to break the tie so you have to "
        "figure that out yourself. Play Rock-Paper-Scissors or arm wrestle or knife fight. I don't "
        "fucking care.\n\n"

        "This game is recommended for 5+ players. As in, more than five players. But yes, also for "
        "people over the age of five.\n\n"

        "Note: The instructions above assume the default settings.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">Gameplay</string>

    <string-array name="round_times_options">
        <item>10 seconds</item>
        <item>20 seconds</item>
        <item>30 seconds</item>
        <item>40 seconds</item>
        <item>50 seconds</item>
        <item>60 seconds</item>
        <item>69 seconds</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="round_times_values">
        <item>10</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>69</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">App Preferences</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
</resources>
